DEBANJAN GHOSH

A software developer with 2 years of experience in an investment bank, working on middleware applications as well as end to end systems. An enthusiastic, self-motivated person with good analytical, logical and problem solving skills. A team worker and enjoys working with a diverse group of people.

S	ki	lls

Java	•	•	•	•	0
Spring	•	•	0	0	0
JavaScript	•	•	•	•	0
AngularJS	•	•	•	0	0
HTML/CSS	•	•	•	•	0
Databases	•	•	•	0	0

Education

University of Southampton BSc. Computer Science (2:1),	2010 - 2014
Peter Symonds College, Winchester Mathematics, Further Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry,	2007 - 2009
Maharana Mewar Public School, India Mathematics , Science , English , Sanskrit ,	2002 - 2007
Social Science(History, Economics, Geography),	

Experiences

2014 - Pi	resent
-----------	--------

JP Morgan Chase & Co, Technical Analyst

Business Activity Monitoring(BAM): Currently working in an agile feature team on the 'one stop shop' operations dashboard for payment interventions and BAM alert management. This includes end to end development using Java, UM MQ, Spring, JavaScript/AngularJS. Currently been involved in UI development for the new BAM interface, using Javascript(ES6) along with Angular JS, HTML and Sass

Accounting Manager: Middleware application written in Java that allows one of the payment system to send real time postings to another system with Cassandra as the persistence layer.

July 2013 - September 2013

JP Morgan Chase & Co, Technology Intern

Developed a reference implementation for deploying business applications to an application server using a release automation tool and documented the complete deployment process

June 2012 - September 2012

ORCHID Project - University of Southampton, Project Support Analyst

Worked as a Web Developer using Python/Django framework for the project on 'Intelligent Agents for Electrical Vehicle Charging' and developed the website to be used for the project trials.

2010 - 2012

Southampton University OTC, Officer Cadet

Interests

Playing cricket and racquet sports such as badminton and table tennis Volunteering at the local aviary Producing music